[Music]
[音乐]
vanessa that was different effect was wrong in hall h symbol the samples
凡妮莎（Hanessa）的效果不同
that's so cool and if you can live it too
太酷了，如果你也能住的话
tell step you will have less stress in your body in jakarta
告诉自己，在雅加达，您的身体压力将减少
the capital of indonesia he ghosts with henry moon and peering when there is about book
在有书本的情况下，他与印度尼西亚的亨利·月亮（Henry Moon）一起窥视着印尼首都
about stoicism cold philosophy terrace with your start with national bestseller and
关于斯多葛主义冷哲学平台，从您的国家畅销书开始，以及
the books or mr team 1019 this kind of documentary explore swine
书籍或先生团队1019这种纪录片探索猪
many indonesians seem to be interested in ancient
许多印尼人似乎对古代
philosophy of the west [Music]
西方哲学[音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
he with henry and the rest of or the cartels business district we are in
他和亨利以及我们所在的卡特尔商业区的其余部分一起
joyce him off and together new sisters what before i wish you can or stoot is
让他高兴起来，和新姐妹们在一起，在我希望你能还是以前之前，是什么？
one was already put to the test one on the major obstacles in jakarta
一个已经在雅加达的主要障碍上进行了测试
traffic and specially greengrass our de metro plus turns into one week traffic
交通，特别是绿草，我们的地铁加上变成了一周的交通
and even though he feltham education lucas leads my taxi alright in
即使他感到哈瑟姆教育卢卡斯带领我的出租车行进去
order to try to my destination with the spigot nice snow acutely
为了用尖顶好雪试一试我的目的地
remembered that the traffic north arrival at my destination
记得北边的交通到达我的目的地
norm en dries reaction to may be in a light is not in my control
规范会促使人们可能无法控制自己的反应
therefore if you how to worry about the sphinx
因此，如果您如何担心狮身人面像
what henry was suffering is like i like the traffic
亨利遭受的痛苦就像我喜欢交通
that the turn out to be the judges the because of dissenting protest from paragraph
原来是法官，是因为对本段提出了异议
you will buy more that stoicism helps him
你会买更多的东西，坚忍的精神可以帮助他
jakarta i aim to confront that first daily base is jakarta
雅加达我打算面对的第一个日常基地是雅加达
Matthew is pleasant but there is more space to get
马修（Matthew）令人愉快，但仍有更多空间
you stuff more old-time fact that dust in graphics
您会在图形中显示灰尘，这是一个更古老的事实
he who can with mars camera traffic no longer borders my philosophy terrace
能够通过火星摄像头访问的人不再是我的哲学平台
the teil or henry's book is indonesian for philosophy or the porch
泰尔或亨利的书是印尼语的哲学或门廊
just like that, there was a lot with the first on a ban
就像这样，第一个禁令有很多
a very accessible in this line which not very
在这条线中非常容易访问的
academy for gmail indonesian glue and toe has that beast and city philosophy
gmail印尼胶和脚趾学院具有野兽和城市哲学
and the risks now rotate is a sector that is only nocebo
现在风险在轮换，这是一个唯一的领域
he says that is not clinical depression 'henry in the Middle Ages
他说，这不是中世纪的临床抑郁症“亨利”
discovered stoicism when put this philosophy into practice and manage to
将这种哲学付诸实践并设法
overcome, both the pression and the jassen brouwersdijk glass media were depressed
克服压力，brouwersdijk玻璃介质的涂层被压低
The premium cookware is also one I was against Nation of Repression afterward
高档炊具也是我后来反对民族压制的一种
to choose you and the key to the coach or therapy from which this can be done is back home
选择您，可以完成此任务的教练或疗法的钥匙就回到了家
to book first of massimo's beauties
首先预定massimo的美女
again star in shanghai many philosophy had a great way to define what i've got
再次成为上海的明星许多哲学有一个很好的方法来定义我所拥有的
for cfs and eye candy af medication to work pg i am my psychiatry like
对于CFS和眼药AF药物工作PG我是我的精神病学喜欢
on plaster
在石膏上
the popular tee or henry's book in tripoli mainly because demonize
在Tripoli上流行的T恤或Henry的书，主要是因为妖魔化了
songs circumstances seen to make it unlikely the countries
歌曲的情况使这些国家不太可能
home to the largest islam i population in the world
世界上最大的伊斯兰教徒i的家园
that ran for so long site Catholic Protestant
运行了这么长时间的天主教新教徒
hindus buddhists and computer nest religion place a very important role in
印度教佛教徒和计算机巢穴宗教在
indonesian culture blasphemy is the legal 5
印尼文化亵渎是合法的5
for the real life and red apple where the devil be from sir
为了现实生活和红苹果，魔鬼来自先生
his is a radio very soft beats things in lisa sparxxx i have
他的收音机非常轻快，我在丽莎·斯帕克斯（Lisa sparxxx）里有节奏
want sympathetic games the most common i want is the split in
想要有同情心的游戏，我想要的最常见的是拆分
in fact in hathaway compatible pico's agency and now i want in this for with
事实上，在兼容Hathaway的pico代理商中，现在我想要
people to feel so angry try lesson pilot cloth that rests list
人们感到非常生气尝试休息的课程
toby list jealous of labor and those tits are big try
托比清单嫉妒劳动，那些山雀是一个很大的尝试
think something else here since the book for skin participated what he thinks
因为皮肤书参与了他的想法，所以在这里想一些其他的事情
an i what is cinesneak
我是什么电影院
faulty books builds stories and the game and national bestseller
错误的书籍会建立故事，游戏和全国畅销书
indicates that many indonesians an open mind it in off to welcome a western
表示许多印尼人都敞开心mind地欢迎西方人
philosophy that is into the point and religious
指向重点和宗教性的哲学
lanscape my focus especialy 31 site or the
lanscape我的焦点尤其是31网站或
philosophy just how is it live in particular how
哲学到底是如何生活的，特别是如何生活的
you manage negative emotions so ideal managing the tv motions is work
您可以管理负面情绪，因此理想的方法是管理电视动作
is a distant you for so sadiq necklaces fate of people want to know
人们对命运的了解如此之遥
more and here's some kind of law isn't
而且这里的某些法律不是
based on village in such an imam and someone from in the background can
基于这样一个伊玛目的村庄，而背景中的某人可以
acces village because teachings her a yard of practice and soul just knew here
进入村庄是因为教给她一个练习场，而灵魂只在这里知道
in wismar fate or the real earth pioneer intresting and wanting barbecues
在维斯马命运还是真正的地球先驱们想要并想要烧烤
stoicism and religion don't has to exclude each other in fact the
坚忍与宗教并不一定要彼此排斥
indonesian case cover city tour philosophy can even en reach en excisting religious
印尼案例封面城市旅游哲学甚至可以达到宗教信仰
experience aardenburg of course most and operational
当然最能体验到阿登堡的运作
and religion where together or now she may still say you will
和宗教在一起或现在她可能仍会说你会
also really you this a new leader in hague talk my region business very
真的，您这是海牙的一位新领导人，我非常在意我所在地区的业务
interesting parsec analyzer is online i say
我说有趣的parsec分析器在线
you my panties basic tennis or my own face solaris no fun fitness
你我的内裤基本网球或我自己的脸没有乐趣健身
in an oil gas current political climate and their presence of religious
在当前的石油政治气候中以及他们的宗教信仰
tent shan's store hissing and helping shirley is teachings can inspire people
帐篷山的商店嘶嘶声和帮助谢利是教义可以启发人们
to be more to learn and manage more narrowly about a popular opinion or belief
更多地了解和管理流行的观点或信念
systems and don't forget to mend an aspects of life that all citizens of the
系统，不要忘了修补生活中的所有公民
global village thing to so if things like work and
全球村的事情，如果像工作和生活这样的事情
friendly people financial problems relationships and of
友好的人财务问题的关系和
course the hear if traffic games my group has my book wants in speyer
当然可以听我的团队是否有我想要的交通游戏
some older alters to write on the subject for at least it along and map spudgy
一些较旧的更改，至少要针对该主题写一些东西，并进行地图欺骗
shirt by translate popular books in class
上课时翻译热门书籍的衬衫
like the workshop massimo beauty or donald robertson
像马西莫美工作室或唐纳德·罗伯森
pinto in the mission and which is that happens and then the maze
在任务中平移，然后发生，然后进入迷宫
fraction deaf child to juice ibo in price that was adrie I think
我认为价格适中的聋哑儿童要喝果汁ibo
belt in very small but his book philosophy terrace
皮带很小，但他的著作哲学平台
shirley statue and bridge with mini indonesian people and the treasures of
雪莉雕像和迷你印尼人与宝藏的桥梁
hélène philosophy [Music]
élène哲学[音乐]
thank you for watching [Music]
谢谢您的收看[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]